asaptickets.com 2019-12-14

# Asaptickets.com Privacy Policy

_Effective May 25, 2018_

ITN respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal data. This policy describes ITN practices regarding personally identifiable information and data (“personal information”). This policy applies to our websites, applications, email and text messages, and social media accounts (the “Platforms”). When you use the Platforms, you agree to the terms in this policy.

###  **PURPOSE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

This privacy policy aims to give you information on how ITN collects and processes your personal data, including any data you may provide through the Platforms when you purchase a product or service or sign up to our newsletter.

The Platforms are not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.

It is important that you read this privacy policy together with any other privacy policy or fair processing policy we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This privacy policy supplements other notices and privacy policies and is not intended to override them.

###  **CONTROLLER**

ITN is the controller and responsible for your personal data.

We have appointed a data protection officer (DPO) who is responsible for overseeing questions in relation to this privacy policy. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact the DPO using the details set out below.

###  **CONTACT DETAILS**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our privacy practices, please contact our DPO in the following ways:  Full name of legal entity: International Travel Network, LLC  Email address: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#19696b706f787a6059786a78696d707a727c6d6a377a7674)

###  **CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY AND YOUR DUTY TO INFORM US OF CHANGES**

We keep our privacy policy under regular review.

It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current. Please keep us informed if your personal data changes during your relationship with us.

###  **THE CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We may collect, use, store and transfer different kinds of personal data about you which we have grouped together as follows:

  1. Identity Data includes [first name, maiden name, last name, username or similar identifier, title, date of birth and gender].
  2. Contact Data includes [billing address, delivery address, email address and telephone numbers].
  3. Financial Data includes [bank account and payment card details].
  4. Transaction Data includes [details about payments to and from you and other details of products and services you have purchased from us].
  5. Technical Data includes [internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform, and other technology on the devices you use to access this website].
  6. Profile Data includes [your username and password, purchases or orders made by you, your interests, preferences, feedback and survey responses].
  7. Usage Data includes [information about how you use our website, products and services].
  8. Marketing and Communications Data includes [your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences].

We also collect, use and share Aggregated Data such as statistical or demographic data for any purpose. Aggregated Data could be derived from your personal data but is not considered personal data in law as this data will not directly or indirectly reveal your identity. For example, we may aggregate your Usage Data to calculate the percentage of users accessing a specific website feature. However, if we combine or connect Aggregated Data with your personal data so that it can directly or indirectly identify you, we treat the combined data as personal data which will be used in accordance with this privacy policy.

#### Platform information

When you visit the Platforms, we may collect information from you. Some of it may be personal information. This information can include search history, IP address, screen resolution, browser used, operating system and settings, access times and referring URL. If you are using a mobile device, we may also collect data that identifies your device, your settings and your location.

#### Booking information

If you book a travel product via the Platforms, we may need additional information from you. This information can include your name (and traveler’s if different) name, age, birthday, gender, passport number, redress control number, email address, telephone number, credit card information, billing address, itinerary and frequent flyer details.

#### Information

We will collect your email address, password and home airport, and other preference information you provide us.

#### Consumer support

If you choose to contact our consumer support services we will collect any inquires, complaint or other information that you may submit to our support team.

When you give us personal information, you are telling us that the information is true, accurate, complete and current. You are also telling us that you have the authorization to provide it to us.

We do not collect any Special Categories of Personal Data about you (this includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health, and genetic and biometric data). Nor do we collect any information about criminal convictions and offences.

###  **IF YOU FAIL TO PROVIDE PERSONAL DATA**

Where we need to collect personal data by law, or under the terms of a contract we have with you, and you fail to provide that data when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract we have or are trying to enter into with you (for example, to provide you with goods or services). In this case, we may have to cancel a product or service you have with us but we will notify you if this is the case at the time.

###  **HOW WE COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We use different methods to collect data from and about you including through:

#### Personal information you give to us

We collect your personal information directly from you. For example, when you provide us your personal information when you register or book travel, contact our customer support. This includes personal data you provide when you:

  1. apply for our products or services;
  2. subscribe to our service or publications;
  3. request marketing to be sent to you;
  4. give us feedback or contact us.

One of the main collection methods are VOICE CALLS. We have vested interest to ensure you have chosen the best possible option. Voice calls are an exclusive opportunity to provide you with an immediate customer support and disclose additional product features, you might not notice on website. Usually, we call back on your request. Sometimes there might be unfinished conversations regarding current flights (misunderstanding in live chat, email system error, poor internet connection etc.), which require immediate response. We don’t make unwanted telemarketing robocalls or any annoyed advertising campaigns. You can opt-out this communication any time by contacting us via phone or email.

#### Personal information we collect passively

We also collect your personal information passively. For example, we collect information about you over time and across different Web sites when you visit this Platform. We also use tracking tools like cookies and beacons. As you interact with our website, we will automatically collect Technical Data about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns. We collect this personal data by using cookies and other similar technologies.

Platform features may make use of your device attributes and settings that will allow us to determine your physical location. Such technologies may include IP address mapping, WiFi, GPS signals, cell tower positioning or other technologies. We use this information to enhance and personalize your experience and provide you with offers and services that may be of interest to you. For example, we may help you find your closest hotel or send you messages that may be of interest to you based on your current location. ITN does not have control over your device settings, but we do recommend enabling location services on your device so you can take advantage of the location based features and functionality offered.

#### Personal information we receive from third parties:

We collect your personal information from third parties. This can include when you log in using a third party platform, such as Facebook. In addition, we also integrate third party software that collects information about users for security reasons.

###  **FOR WHAT PURPOSE WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We will use your personal information in the following ways:

#### Improving our services

To provide you and improve our Platforms and services, to better understand the users of our Platforms and services, and to protect our property and to prevent damage to them.

#### Bookings

We and our travel partners use your personal information to process your bookings and store your itinerary information where applicable.

#### Marketing activities

We use your information for marketing purposes. These activities may include

  1. To send you marketing emails and/or text messages from a ITN address regarding our services or those of our partners, if you have opted-in to receive emails and/or text messages from us or have transacted with us, and as permitted by law. You can easily unsubscribe from these marketing communications at any time by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link included in the newsletter or by texting STOP via sms. PEWC for Email subscription: By entering your email address and clicking "JOIN NOW" button on subscribe forms on the Website, you agree to receive Email promotions from Asaptickets.com. Unsubscribe at any time. No purchase necessary. You also agree to our R&Cs. PEWC for SMS subscription: By entering your phone number and clicking on "JOIN NOW" button on subscribe forms on the Website, you provide your signature and consent to receive automated text messages with promotions from Asaptickets.com. Msg & data rates may apply. Text STOP to quit at any time. No purchase necessary. You also agree to our R&Cs.
  2. To display more relevant advertising and recommendations, or suppress advertising and content that you might find irrelevant. This advertising might be shown to you on our Platforms as well as third party platforms (including social media sites) and include information or offers that we, or our business partners’, believe you will find interesting.Individualized advertising may be based on information collected through cookies or other tracking technologies.
  3. If you choose to participate in promotional activities, relevant information may be used to administer these promotions.

To communicate with you, including as follows:

  1. To send booking confirmations;
  2. To send alerts and notifications you have subscribed to, including to your mobile device;
  3. To solicit reviews;
  4. To update you regarding itineraries processed by our service;
  5. To communicate with you if you have contacted ITN consumer support;
  6. To send you information servicing and administrative emails;
  7. To send you information about services, offered by ITN or our business partners, that we believe you would be interested in;

#### Legal purposes

In certain cases we may need to use your information to handle and resolve legal disputes, for regulatory investigations and compliance or to enforce the terms of use of the service.

#### Performance of a contract

The use of your personal information may be necessary to perform the services and provide you products that you have requested from us. For example, if you make a booking on our Platform, we need to collect personal information from you in order to complete the booking.

#### Consent

We may rely on your consent to use your data for certain direct marketing purposes. You can withdraw your consent anytime by contacting us.

We have set out below, in a table format, a description of all the ways we plan to use your personal data.

 **Purpose/Activity**|  **Type of data**  
---|---  
To register you as a new customer| 

(a) Identity

(b) Contact  
  
To process and deliver your order including:

(a) Manage payments, fees and charges

(b) Collect and recover money owed to us

| 

(a) Identity

(b) Contact

(c) Financial

(d) Transaction

(e) Marketing and Communications  
  
To manage our relationship with you which will include:

(a) Notifying you about changes to our terms or privacy policy

(b) Asking you to leave a review or take a survey

| 

(a) Identity

(b) Contact

(c) Profile

(d) Marketing and Communications  
  
To administer and protect our business and this website (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data)

| 

(a) Identity

(b) Contact

(c) Technical  
  
To deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you| 

(a) Identity

(b) Contact

(c) Profile

(d) Usage

(e) Marketing and Communications

(f) Technical  
  
To use data analytics to improve our website, products/services, marketing, customer relationships and experiences| 

(a) Technical

(b) Usage  
  
To make suggestions and recommendations to you about goods or services that may be of interest to you| 

(a) Identity

(b) Contact

(c) Technical

(d) Usage

(e) Profile

(f) Marketing and Communications  
  
###  **YOUR CHOICES**

Generally, we do not rely on consent as a legal basis for processing your personal data although we will get your consent before sending third party direct marketing communications to you via email or text message

Marketing email has an opt-out URL and you can unsubscribe from such communication at any time. You cannot unsubscribe from servicing emails and administrative messages.

###  **HOW WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

#### Corporate affiliates and change of control

We may share your personal information with our corporate affiliates and if ITN itself (or part of its business) is sold or otherwise changes control, owners would have access to your personal information for the uses set out herein.

#### Service providers

We may share your personal information with suppliers who perform services on our behalf and have agreed in writing to protect and not further disclose your information.

#### Payment service providers and travel vendors

If you book through the Platforms, we may share your personal information with the payment service providers and the travel vendors you have booked with. This can include online travel agencies, hotels, airlines, car rental companies, and travel insurance providers. These third parties will process your personal information as data controllers in accordance with their own privacy policies. If you contact our consumer support, they may need to share information about your request with the relevant travel vendor in order to assist you.

#### Business partners

We may share your personal information with various business partners. Some of these business partners may use your personal information for fraud detection found, include, but not limited, for an email address, for detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues. We may also share your information for ask our partner to create a survey, form, application, or questionnaire, for the purpose to know the degree of your satisfaction with our services. Some of these business partners may use your personal information for online behavioral advertising purposes, or to offer you services or products that we believe you may be interested in. We may also share your information as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. We may also share anonymous aggregated usage information with partners.

We enter into confidentiality and data processing terms with partners to ensure they comply with high levels of confidentiality and best practice in privacy and security standards and we regularly review these standards and practices.

#### Trips shared by you

If you use or have itineraries as part of our Service, you can send or grant access to your itinerary to anyone you choose. Your itinerary may contain enough details (for example, booking reference codes) to allow the recipient to cancel or modify your booking, perform a check-in, etc. You should only share your itinerary with people you trust. If you choose to display your itinerary on publicly-viewable web pages (Facebook, for instance), that information may be collected and used by others.

#### Information shared in public

If you provide us a review of your trip, you authorize us to publish it on all our Platforms under the screen name you provided. You also authorize us to aggregate it with other reviews.

#### Authorities

We may disclose personal information if required by law, for example to law enforcement or other authorities. This includes court orders, subpoenas and orders arising from legal processes, and administrative or criminal investigations. We may also disclose your personal information if the disclosure is necessary for the prevention, detection or prosecution of criminal acts or to prevent other damage, or in response to a legal action or to enforce our rights and claims.

We may also share anonymous aggregated usage information with others.

###  **HOW WE STORE AND PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

As a customer-oriented business we respect and value your expectations. As a result, you are able to make announcements and queries at any time regarding your concerns in privacy matters. Each of our marketing email has an opt-out button and you can change preferences or unsubscribe at all from such communication at any time. Each ITN website is targeted to the current audience and region, therefore subscribe/unsubscribe options are also different. You cannot unsubscribe from servicing emails and administrative messages.

###  **RETENTION PERIODS**

We will only retain your personal data for as long as reasonably necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, regulatory, tax, accounting or reporting requirements. We may retain your personal data for a longer period in the event of a complaint or if we reasonably believe there is a prospect of litigation in respect to our relationship with you.

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal, regulatory, tax, accounting or other requirements.

###  **COOKIES**

Our servers and data centers are located in the U.S and our service providers may be located there and in other countries. By providing us PI, you agree that your PI may be transferred to and stored in these countries. These countries may have different and/or less stringent privacy/data protection and data security rules than those of your own country. As a result, your PI may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in those countries according to laws in those countries. Subject to the applicable laws of such countries, we will provide the necessary safeguards to maintain protections of your PI, e.g. by obtaining from the PI recipients contractual commitments based on the EU model clauses. ITN has a security program intended to keep the PI stored in our systems protected from unauthorized access and misuse. Our systems are configured with data encryption, or scrambling technologies and firewalls constructed to industry standards. We also use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology that protects the PI you send over the Internet. PI may only be accessed by persons within our organizations, or our service providers to carry out the uses indicated in this Privacy Policy. We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your PI from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your PI to those employees, agents, contractors and other service providers who have a business need to know. They will only process your PI on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality. We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected PI breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.

###  **OTHER WEBSITES**

If you click through to third party websites or other platforms, ITN’s privacy policy does not apply.

###  **CHILDREN**

ITN does not knowingly collect personal information from minors. If we become aware that a minor is attempting to submit personal information, we will remove this information from our records. If you are the parent/legal guardian of a minor who has given us personal information, please contact us so we can delete it.

###  **THIRD-PARTY MARKETING**

Under certain circumstances set by applicable law, you are entitled to:  

  * **Request access** to your PI (commonly known as a “data subject access request”). This enables you to receive a copy of the PI we hold about you and to check correctness and integrity of PI. The disclosure might be limited to the 12-month period preceding the receipt of verifiable request. You may also request to furnish you with:   
    * the categories of sources from which PI is collected;
    * the business or commercial purposes for collecting of PI;
    * the categories of third parties with whom we share your PI;
    * the categories of PI we have disclosed for a business purpose.
  * **Request correction** of the PI that we hold about you. This enables you to request any incomplete or inaccurate PI to be corrected, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new PI you provide to us.
  * **Request to delete.** You are able to submit verifiable request and ask us to delete your PI. Please, be aware, there are some cases, when we might reject your request (e.g. when we shall comply with legal obligation or complete a transaction requested by you).
  * **Request to opt out** from PI sales. Such requests shall be submitted through the “Do Not Sell My Personal Information” website.

Due to the remote nature of our services, it is important for us to keep communicating through the same email (Verified Email), which was used by you to request a price quote or purchase air tickets and other related services. The Verified Email is the key communication channel for us, so we can give quick answers and not to divulge your data to any malicious person. You might also submit request through the voice call, but still we must use the Verified Email to reply, due to law requirements and in order to protect our legal claims. **NONDISCRIMINATION:**  We shall not discriminate (deny services, charge different prices, provide different levels of quality) against you because you exercised any of the rights set herein. This right might be limited in case, if  the difference in prices or levels or quality is reasonably related to the value provided to you by your PI.   We might obtain your opt-in consent and provide to you financial incentives, so you agree to provide additional PI or not to request the deletion of your PI. **FEES and DENIALS:** You will not have to pay a fee to access your PI (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive (more than twice in a 12-month period) or excessive. Alternatively, we could refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances. We might also refuse to act on your request, when we are not in a position to identify you and verify your request. We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your PI (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that PI is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you (via email, phone or messenger) to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response. **TERMS:** We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it could take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated. The maximum response time shall not exceed 90 days. **CONTACTS:** you can submit your complaint/ request to DPO email (see above) or by filling the Request Form.

###  **OPTING OUT**

You can ask us or third parties to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by logging into the website and checking or unchecking relevant boxes to adjust your marketing preferences or by contacting us at any time.

###  **CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY**

We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice. We will notify you of material changes to how we use your personal information prior to implementing them. We may notify you about such a material change by email or prominent notice on our website. By using our services and Platforms after we post these changes, you indicate you accept them.

###  **CHANGE OF PURPOSE**

We will only use your personal data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If you wish to get an explanation as to how the processing for the new purpose is compatible with the original purpose, please contact us.

If we need to use your personal data for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and we will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.

Please note that we may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent, in compliance with the above rules, where this is required or permitted by law.

###  **YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS**

Under certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data.

#### Request access

to your personal data (commonly known as a “data subject access request”). This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.

#### Request correction

of the personal data that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you corrected, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new data you provide to us.

#### Withdraw consent

at any time where we are relying on consent to process your personal data. However, this will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent. If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide certain products or services to you. We will advise you if this is the case at the time you withdraw your consent.

If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, please contact us.

###  **NO FEE USUALLY REQUIRED**

You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we could refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.

###  **WHAT WE MAY NEED FROM YOU**

We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.

###  **TIME LIMIT TO RESPOND**

We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it could take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated.

###  **ITN USES TRACKING TOOLS SUCH AS COOKIES**

We (or our suppliers) use several common tracking tools. We use these tools to collect usage and demographic information about you over time and across different Web sites when you use our Platforms. We also have third parties (e.g. advertisers) that collect personal information this way. Tools we use may include browser cookies. Your browser will store these cookies on your computer in a small file.

We and our advertising partners may also use web beacons (single pixel GIF images). These web beacons are placed in the code of a Web page or an email newsletter. When you access a partner site within our mobile applications, we may track your activity on that site.

By using the Platforms, you give us your free, unambiguous and informed consent to the use of any of the cookies and tracking tools mentioned in this policy.

ITN uses tracking tools for following purposes

  1. To track new visitors to the Platforms.
  2. To help us recognize your browser as a previous visitor. This includes saving and remembering any preferences that may have been set while your browser was visiting the Platforms, such as language.
  3. To make use of cross-device tracking in order to optimize our advertising activities. As part of cross-device tracking, ITN may combine information collected from a particular browser or mobile device with another computer or device linked to the computer or device from which the information was collected. By changing your cookie settings on your device you can change your cross-device tracking settings for advertising purposes.
  4. To work with online advertising companies to display targeted advertising on our Platforms and third party platforms that you visit. This targeting may be based on information you submit on our Platforms or third party platforms. This targeting may also be based on your activities or behaviors on our Platforms or those of third parties. We may also obtain information about your browsing history from our business partners
  5. To track when you book on partner websites
  6. To help improve our website offering and for capacity planning purposes. We or our third party service providers may set analytics cookies. These allow us to gather aggregated or segmented information about the types of visitors that access our Platforms and the pages and advertisements that they view. In order to better understand your use of our Platforms, we or our third party service providers may collect information on such use, including pages visited, links clicked and mouse movements. We do not use this information to personally identify you.

###  **HOW YOU CAN CONTROL TRACKING TOOLS AND OPT-OUT OF ONLINE BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING**

Your browser may give you the ability to control cookies. How to do this varies from browser to browser. You should view the Help menu on the browser you use for further information. Your opt out choice is stored in opt out cookies only in that browser, so you should separately set your preferences for other browsers, computers, or devices you may use. If your browser blocks cookies, your opt out preferences may not be effective. Deleting browser cookies can remove your opt out preferences, so you should visit this page periodically to review your preferences. If you block or delete cookies or opt out of online behavioral advertising, not all of the tracking that we have described in this policy will stop.

Please also note that opting out of a third party cookie does not mean that you will no longer receive or be subject to online advertising or marketing. It means that the third party service from which you opted out will no longer deliver ads tailored to your web preferences and online behavioral.

We may also use Google Analytics to collect demographic and interest data about you (such as age, gender, and interests), including through Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. We may use the information collected about you through Google Analytics for Google services such as Remarketing with Google Analytics and Google Display Network Impression Reporting. Choices you make are browser and device specific. Some aspects of our site use cookies to function. You may not be able to use these features if you set your device to block cookies.

###  **HOW ITN RESPONDS TO “DO NOT TRACK” SIGNALS**

Some browsers have a “Do Not Track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. These features are not yet uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to those signals.

##  **How to Save on Your Next Booking**

###### Subscribe to Receive Our Special Offers & Cheap Deals!

 **AND/OR**

you can totally do both!

100% Privacy Guaranteed! No Purchase Necessary. Unsubscribe/text STOP at any time. By entering your phone number and/or email and clicking on “JOIN NOW“, you consent to receive occasional promotional SMS and/or Emails from Asaptickets.com. You also agree to our T&Cs and Privacy Policy

## One Stop **Shopping**

Exclusive Airfare Contracts and Insider Consolidator Deals

Discount Hotels, Rental Cars and Transfer Bookings

Authorized Airline Travel Agency Since 2001

24/7/365 Excellent Service Provided by 850 Live Travel Agents

Concierge Service Helps to Save Time, Money and Simplify Flight
